Descend into fear.
Black Water: Abyss is a horror, action, adventure
film directed by Andrew Traucki.
An adventure-loving couple convince their friends to explore a remote,
uncharted cave system in the forests of Northern Australia.
With a tropical storm approaching, they abseil into the mouth of the cave, but when the caves start to
flood, tensions rise as oxygen levels fall and the friends find themselves trapped.
Unknown to them, the storm has also brought in a pack
of dangerous and hungry crocodiles.
Jennifer, played by Jessica McNamee.
Eric, played by Luke Mitchell.
Yolanda, played by Amali Golden.
Viktor, played by Benjamin Hoetjes.
Cash, played by Anthony J. Sharpe.
Akito, played by Louis Toshio Okada.
Black Water: Abyss is a 2020 Australian horror film directed by Andrew Traucki.
It is a standalone sequel to Black Water (2007).
In the film, a group of friends venture in deep forests of
Australia to explore a remote cave system.
However, when a tropical storm hits and rising flood waters trap them deep below the surface,
something even deadlier emerges from the darkness—a large killer crocodile.
It was released on July 10, 2020.
The film explores themes of australia, cave, animal attack, survival, creature.
The tone is dark.